okay good morning Sasha how did you have
good sleep at Yonsei the Hama if you
didn't have good sleep you can sleep in
the class
nobody mail say how to hard case I would
occur sound sleep the very experienced
student or Malaysia juniors in the
session they learned to sleep like this
in camera she'll protect cocktails a
nice hotel don't go like this for y'all
Jonesy go like this it's hell and then
sleep with city chances are very
advanced student after 20 years the
Arsenal fatal results this initiation
okay let's do meditation amazing a
dimension that's easy chance to sleep
Las Vegas a technology way
if you'd like to record it it's a good
time to record it you're gonna say
eluding the ha ha take a mean solution
I'll just show you how to see what you
can use it at home because a Chinaman's
your further a week so it's it's a lot
it's a total Joe
after that I think you you won't need it
okay that's a colony Topo Gigio take a
loo England please don't put on widget
does it seem we have found our way
singsong don't put on internet we are
found out another one Lois I guess you
Michael will get trouble okay see
Michael my fancy Michael won't be able
to come to China can see my Kazumi burn
fat you don't wanna so be responsible so
I think that's a full heart a cancer
yeah okay here we go
ha ha
we're gonna go a little bit farther this
time so we'll go through each step a
little bit faster commentates in a fight
so you're anything so he may be
Buddhahood sound a little crazy so it's
important to do your meditation and keep
moving - Tommy Sanders your whole entire
audience in the arts to shoot that one
Jinzo
otherwise you will get sleepy Brenda
honey who I found Quinta ok here we go
oh my gosh - relax your face fellas only
the Liam Liam boo
relax your I found Sony the EMP relax
your ma falzone's a bath relax your
shoulder fell so near a temple relax
your fingers
fellas only the shoulder and pull in
your stomach just a little bit shall we
the natio football
and then come to the sound of the air
conditioning hole I tau conk out the
singing song this is like the ground
floor of a nine story hotel so choice a
shaker chosen to attend the deep yummy
ito
we counted as zero woman's sons or
dealings home and rest your head sorry
rest your mind on the sound of the air
conditioner like you rest your head on
your pillow chauhan pathogens a gentle
showing young bunny the ish since I take
account of the singing shock Fanta show
me
and then please come to the beating of
your heart the whole team that's a light
our sintió show you are in your body the
iodine is Chantilly you're looking down
haka at the beating of your heart kinda
seen the totem
now let's go to the inside of the heart
since all men should are seeing the Nabu
more quiet place gongchan and Ginga the
fun the walls of the heart are beating
around me seen chance I was told our
thought Kyoto and the inside of the
heart is like a beautiful small
apartment sankaran April Josh Anika
Peyton since it con you with lots of
sunlight yongkang's home pain
now we go to the very center of the
heart since a woman shoot our Tsingtao
doesn't own scene in the walls of the
heart beating faraway scene challenge I
against who
Kyoto almost cannot hear them see who is
in question Poochyena but still lots of
sunlight and very comfortable elegant
meditation space vengeance showman a
young Gwang government officials who
should mention kanji Andy
next to me in that inner room now holds
I found Jenny sell shrimp um it's a
small table see each other shall towards
and on that table is a small pot of
sugar it's a child towards the shot me
and uh chief a pound and I put my finger
in the sugar
Oh bah so to send out pal Hurley and I
see on the tip of my finger no hole it's
a candle with the GGN shop there's a
small crystal of sugar because I was out
the family and to show my meditation
power we're not sure what that means how
dealio I will put my mind inside one
single grain of sugar okay about what
the yeast fans I'd say you could see I
was out the tunnel eating teeny so it's
like I open a door in the sugar crystal
- huh Santa Carla panting tip a Sandman
and I put my mind inside what about the
issue found out a limit and I'm
surprised to see now and Jean she does
shit inside it's another beautiful
sunlit meditation telling me oh she knew
why he got so many unwanted means sound
fun
so try to focus your mind on a single
tiny point so it's how such return to
Anita years I - I saw the CDN shop and
meditate inside that point sorry Etienne
the name Nemean
napal so Misha
now let's expand the mind since I
remember yeesh
Colson the mind itself becomes the
Pacific Ocean you should mention be
enchanting EPN typing young it stretches
from China to Los Angeles from Hong Kong
it's cost quad sense no sense e deep and
shun quiet an engine and it's my whole
mind a step ahead
what some goodies Josiah pian hye-young
so inside the sugar crystal so it's a
searching County limit expand the mine
now education cost that this is not real
meditation we are just warming up our
mind like before she go or something
tapping push attention to me mission
moment yesterday so issue desertion
now please include the sky over the
ocean since I Simba
King Kong yeah Poland Jean line
now we want to go even quieter syndrome
is about shell chica can dancing the
diva try to turn off your mind
johnson-graham be is it's actually not
possible
this is our Shippo condone saw thought
but we pretend that we turn off the mic
Tommy are chitchat so we should 1p if
any thoughts come know where the honey
and whole island then find them and
block them she take out that Battlement
untrue super quiet so cheetah aunty
okay here we go double seven oh my gosh
did she tell
double a tip at home even more quiet
than Giada auntie when thoughts come to
the mind turn attorney intuiting how
easily - aha just let them go gentlemen
chinko like clouds in the sky
Sharon comes on the Endor this is not
coaching so being pushed coaching this
is not real meditation bullshit and
gender means it's just to exercise our
mind muscle to search you in she woman
is zero
during the meditation time in silence
it's in please remember to breathe out
second time shinjite Ohio the arts it
would she
so at the end of the normal exhale sigh
pinch on the hood see that j-hope push
out a little more air
it's I try to attend in the country and
this will keep the G level so the coop
out take a cheetah king home now let's
think of one of our teachers since the
Roman she's sound
anyway lost should think about one of
the great teachers and you're not sound
sound either show what Don's on your way
without the dog shit maybe it's your mom
are done what's your Sunita full mood
scene who are your first grade teachers
Avenue D wait
an officer special school teacher I
always Shoshone mean the people of sure
or the person who taught you your job
was at Arkansas downtown Kinney shout
out urgent or spiritual teacher wasn't
it the shooting solution could be
historical teacher like Buddha face
releases something else appears or for
thought the gardener also and it could
be your heart teacher
yeah casein it sings if you didn't meet
your heart you know Connie in the way
you tend sings to the heart you can
imagine them you can chew sound sound
even if the art teachers that's the way
Jesus Ortega seems to say into sturgeon
you can invite them okay it's you know
Dean Kamen and just imagine they are
sitting in front of you since you choose
Shan Shan patio to a tiny dream in
relaxed found soul they're very happy
that you're meditating panic I seen you
and eat I don't mean some they are
looking at you with
great affection Valentine's and that
Shingen kanjani we make a lot of
mistakes in our life amends I show me so
without so - toe-to-toe but still they
love us like our mother
then imagine n room open somewhat senior
age a woman
so enjoy sitting with your teacher don't
you sound so Knievel of shirts was I
need to knee CK type home they're alive
they are not a picture that miniature
horse at the Horsham zoom that being
pussy tempo pian there are real time as
a change today they are breathing time
and I will see you can see now the
little sweet fragrance from their body
in an NGO and out I mention some chili
that we waited she way San Shi your eyes
are closed the engine should be hood but
you can see them looking at you with
great affection there's any pecan poem
and I said seed addict well hi kangan e
very proud of you
hey Charlie anyway Hall even with all
your mystics now decently finest oil
that's all
now think of something about your
teacher that you really love
since our ascension Danny loves you
since on its and a safe 800 I think some
good quality they have he said I mention
the hopping should choose one chance I
Iike you can change this quality a few
times a week or a few weeks
sorry Jai Alai the seeker since you
can't only catch a Shinto gabion take a
pinch it it's you can also change the
teacher you meditate on every few days
near chemical City and Ronnie Wayne
isn't I mean jungle oh sure
that teachers good qualities like the
pen negative shit a hopping Church I
wrote on it should be it's not inside
the teacher pushes a larceny member it's
coming from my seat I should lie to you
what I don't see maybe other people meet
the same teacher harsh apparent you
thought atonia we're not sure and they
don't see these good qualities Chapel a
canteen other say under hopping should
because they don't have those seeds
you may permit me associate owns it so
let's go back to our past life so you
don't man she way Tom interchange shit
we don't have the power many of us to
see our past life directly well men
Tonto and Dorland open me on the D de ke
true JJ I can J woman detention but we
can imagine maybe what we did then we'll
make a G sound so horseshoe and solace
in a city to plant the seeds so
enchanted say she don't see the result
of the seeds is the proof of the seeds
so on sir that's your core oh shit don't
sit tell me
and the results should be similar to the
seed I take a core English second tone
solicitor so I must have done something
very good in my password so it was that
changed beating suits all they said
and how does shit and I will try to
imagine what I did no it's how situation
so what thought you told a segment you
cannot imagine anything that you don't
have a seat for you sir wolf are mm I
see any militants at the channel salads
and other don't see so the highest score
so you take out a shape I will say that
even those imaginations way so we're
short oh Jesus they say something so
they are true because they are coming
from seeds tell me a daughter change it
you know it happen like the lights are
you Thomas it so have fun
so a tree how harsh I'm so relaxed found
so enjoy the
Tasker did which you must have done she
sounds so questioning he thinks it's
over the house should make a nice movie
how you pour hot any you can be anybody
you can show a little cousin man or
woman no hotter than a neoneun you can
have any job okay your hand or the
console you can live in any country okay
mm had a coach ollie you can even be a
special bird or a special fish Neeson's
okay so it should be the your hood it's
it happy to know okay let's make the
movie how I was in that I paid like a
teeny we'll spend a little bit of time
here for my princess attea white and
indecision just relax
so she I found so enjoy just have a show
if you start to get sleepy you're gonna
catch the fan Kuan now or you start to
think about other things what our
characters you sound better don't she
just smile and bring your mind back to
the movie now hold your waist she'll
hoping that you should turn without
deigning me gently
jinda
welcome back dear teacher since I heard
a little of shonali and you can ask
yourself those three questions okay when
it's at a nice angle when T number one
the do they have this beautiful quality
Taman Yomi Ortega may harder pinch it
the answer is yes - Jota number two dr
is that beautiful quality coming from me
think I made hotter pinches a fall guy -
you wore from the seeds I planted in my
past life
that's all you what I change it so it's
on Saturday don't sit and the answer is
yes
- yo time in the third question this
anchor when t is there anything about
that colony which is not coming from me
take a listen a jalapeno sorry Emile
Junkers polite so you water is it
possible to say anything in the world
which I don't have to sit for the
American can doubt sagacity on your
genre people say what it's also a chance
at a time see and the answer is no
passion real and this is comes in are
you to come see that beautiful Cod is
not inside there the mayor the king
should be importantly min being a pain
is not inside the pen but so entropy
pincushions IPD min this is coming from
me I should I - what
and because of that chugging away what's
I can become Buddha or KHL for
let's come back down the hole mentor
while satsang soft landing at the
airplane ma'am and Fiji chan LOH come
back to your mind wait on it initially
the thoughts are coming to the mind like
clouds the entire shall enjoy a young
cowboy ish
and I am not watching them now ho or
premios I can determine when you come
down come down a little bit faster tell
me once had two other shots or quite
Indian and don't forget to take an extra
exhale we all wanted a idiot a writer
would she
let's go down to level seven woman she
tottered she's home a little more noisy
guns how they consolidate India if
thoughts come in the mind
no Bunyan 13 with our Isha leader then
block down lieutenant
they'll come back to the ocean and the
sky turns out Wade out can call you back
enjoy relax
she sounds all she found so we're almost
finished women see way out when China
the mind becomes the ocean no he should
be enjoying appear hye-young while in
deep
kwan/wong person
let's come back to the sugar crystal no
man without tally ting teeny inside
beautiful meditation room with lots of
sunlight immense of age have made the
means and fountain yung kong feet on the
homepage imagine a single sugar crystals
sitting in in the whole ocean to ascend
so you can shout shout us 18 County
and now inside the inside of the heart
since I sigh Cinda momenta name yet
elegant Sunday meditation room nikka
yatta so my young condom in some
function in the walls at the hard are
being far away
Syntel sin child's I even saw Kyoto
now we're inside the heart the close to
the world center - income they can
counting Xin chào the bidding is pretty
strong Cynthia I picked out the mention
and now we're sitting in our body seems
almond sides a little Chantilly in the
room in China so I attack what a fun
journey we are watching her heartbeat
woman's eye cancer diseases India
if I keep doing this meditation no go
watch the streets or take a mini cell I
will truly see how everything around me
is coming from me what your nun
göttingen can down what those other eat
shit or she lights are your water then I
can make the world beautiful now with
your non-going our city in the face
under Mady and I can help everyone
around me okay chip bounce or pigeon so
take three deep exhales so it's all
sensor to show called she imagined that
the breath going out is a golden light
so who's gonna cheat you should sink on
and it touches all the people in this
world so pond out segregation destroy
origin all the animals all the living
creatures so your data or saw your does
show me any blood system ok time in
touch the one day they will do this
emptiness meditation now he Tian's when
you're eating them in your whites or
take a consent means this tenth of the
lion Turkish is the water 3d back there
sensor would she
then take a nice stretch now haha the
Larsen is a centi single and yo mr. Nick
if you guys have microphones will do
some question and answer okay change of
base a microphone where is he went down
when you ask a question
Danny volunteer should put it in pieces
but have fencing quite quite it and then
Stanley can translate the host a
knee-jerk a fake seashell so haha
I want to say I wanna ask two questions
first one is is fundraising planting the
seeds for money because when you say and
if it is what's the returning rate
what's the profit rate because when you
say every time you want 1,000 you give
100 so it's always ten times back okay
isn't it the sister boat every 24 hours
okay good question
I heard of auntie first answer do you go
hey Dad
when you teach Dharma Danny should try
so for five I shouldn't ask for money
supreme guides out yonder it should be
for free in gaseumeun faded my teacher
taught for he taught me for thirty years
when I launched it sound so essentially
in almost every day G homemade you know
gerashenko
he never asked me for any money to pass
on a meal young coworker that's him
when I first met him then what leads to
you ain't I - aha I gave him my bank
book was about what are they eating how
it sound cool but any funny he he took
it he said what is this thing I know he
said the knowledge the caduceus was just
somebody I said it's a bank oh so so so
wha
then he said I don't need it as I'll
push ya
two Emmys and aliens and of course I
kept it so so should be free
so yeah taking as a mere faith but if
the student want to help there's a joke
Oh take it easy
so as I'm missing out lights it's a
pound so like to save the ancient books
to associate son Jesus your coats Indian
I think it's important what you said
Tony other it's not comfortable for me
to ask for money I don't like it she
said whopping pussy hundred now what she
can die Jammu Jyoti Anna what will
people sue fool but I will do it that's
our high so he talked to save the books
when I turned 13 did then how much
interest again you make donation Togo
she woman so gentle way thought out was
how to take a listen it depends on how
happy are you to choose a uni automatic
icing color if you give like this you
can you give up it's a giant Gator okay
then the seed doesn't grow very fast
there's also then you know how - la
gives hundred dollars in the class you
can give happy ok and the seed will go
faster
I don't know in in my diamond company
we start with nothing I have seven
dollars later it was bought by a Warren
Buffett it's about two hundred fifty
million dollars per year so yeah if you
plant happily it can double every my
company double every 18 months for
nineteen years I think it's one of the
fastest in the history of New York City
so if the feeling is happy also choose
carefully make priority we cannot donate
to everything we want to but we don't
have enough money so giving donation is
not easy you think it's easier to give
away money than to make money
but it's not you have to think carefully
what's the most benefit and then you're
supposed to do very gracefully okay and
like that okay second question
okay yeah you do get a lot if you're
fundraising but don't push people only
what people are happy and do legally
what's the law in your country how much
tax you have to pay keep a good record
if the government want to see you you
say this is the record everything should
be legal in your country
okay quick quickly other question first
thing any time you share or you you
share something like the 6/10 book you
have to check the law in your country is
it allowed to share this thing each each
country has different law
so most important he says check ask
people what's the correct how can I do
this correctly secondly sometimes I tell
people just write down a good thing you
didn't why most people only think about
the bad thing they did it's very hard to
get people in every country to do coffee
Minchin
I don't know why we are all most of us
are like that do you keep your book yes
do you check what you're doing during
the day yes how are you doing good or
bad I'm always doing panting okay so
personally I keep it on my computer I
found out I'm thinking more about the
bad thing I did then I'm thinking about
the good thing I did so I made a rule
for myself I have to put the good thing
first then if I died during the book I I
did the rejoicing
more important okay okay more important
so it give equal time equal time do the
good one first and most people will not
give enough time to the good one okay
all right
any other question thank you for good
question where is the okay hi
which means and then having to see
Kushina and Achaia to find objects that
each person sometimes I tend to choose
to material objects because in my memory
since we're good he is always obvious
okay good question
many of us choose Buddha for our
meditation object
but most of the people who choose a
Buddha for meditation object never saw
Buddha we saw painting or we saw statue
the with many of us didn't have enough
seed to meet the Buddha directly but
it's very wonderful to to meditate on
the Buddha as our teacher so it's almost
like Maitreya is if we call the nickname
is the future Buddha next Buddha that
Buddha is much closer than we think we
think on next Buddha come after 1,000
years or something it's not like that
they are very close but if we didn't
meet them yet how to do the meditation
this is in the Jing and it may be
helpful for you we always begin with the
outline when the Buddhist first painting
was made see in those time they don't
have cell phone so and they don't need a
painting of Buddha because they have a
burden then there are three stories in
the Jing of a student who was far away
the one I like the best is a princess
and she lived in Sri Lanka a Buddha was
in North India then she sent him a very
beautiful message with some businessmen
traveling businessmen
did that correspondence is very sweet we
still have the correspondence and it's
like she's in love with him in a pure
way and so he want to send her she said
please send me a picture of you so in
those days they will put a fire here and
Buddha was sitting in front of the fire
and with his back to the fire then
somebody will hold up a sheep and the
Buddhist shadow will come from the fire
to the ship in English we call outline
or silhouette
and they will make exactly correct
Buddha silhouette so in meditation this
is a good system pretend there's a light
behind the teacher and first all you can
see is to get the silhouette correct
then traditionally we start with the
eyes so first there's silhouette then
put the eyes and just floating and they
are looking at you with love they always
say it's important the eyes are looking
at you at large like in high school how
you look at your boyfriend
again like that Buddhist like they love
you okay then you finish the rest of the
face the smile and in the meditation the
teacher is always smiling why all day
long we do small bad things one thing we
do good every day we do our meditation
so but Buddha's happy
okay then you finish the rest of the
hands and clothes they know imagine your
favorite flower smell could be Jasman my
llama smell like good cup of coffee to
me
that's okay okay what smell you enjoy
meditation should be enjoy it should be
fun otherwise you won't do it use your
imagination
Maitreya yeah that's fine but not a
statue never make a statue never make a
flat painting okay that's not meditation
if you want to do that then go to the
temple and look at the painting but it's
only indirect benefit to your mind if
you close your eyes and make a real
person it's much more powerful okay
thank you okay
how are you okay how did you make the
seed to make to meet that statue that's
me you meant Maitreya in your past life
okay definitely okay otherwise you
cannot see the statue okay so you have
the seed but maybe you were sleepy
something so you didn't meet the real
one in this life or maybe you met them
but you didn't realize it
I
okay do you wanna say Joey
No
my answer has three parts okay then
we'll take a break okay
so I was in the diamond business for 19
years it's a truly international
business there are diamond people in
every country and actually it feels a
little bit like a family I went to the
mall here two days ago I've met some
really good diamond people and and we
had a really good time talking about
diamonds you know so I have a friend
he's very wealthy diamond dealer and but
he's very cheap
you know he never gives any donation
he's always fighting for money you know
then I'm worried about him because he
right now he's very successful but I
thought if he keeps like this he will
lose his money his business will fail
and I love him very much so I'm thinking
how to help him you know and finally I
got a good idea I invite him to go to
dinner
what's he what does he say
who's pay I said don't worry don't worry
I pay I think okay okay we can go you
know he's very cheap we go to the dinner
you know and my friends know when I go
to the restaurant I love to give a big
tip you know at least fifty percent
sometimes hundred percent because those
people are working so hard
and also want to make more money so I
give a big I give a big kick to them in
this hotel the people who clean your
room find them today give them a nice
tip okay just from you okay not through
the organization okay and the whole
hotel will be happy today okay so I
thought if he learns to give tip his
income won't go down you know but how to
get him to do the tip so I took him to a
very expensive restaurant
it's called village on the green Tavern
on the Green
in New York City it's a restaurant on
the park the city only allows one
restaurant in the Central Park
so it's very expensive and I took him to
the restaurant then when it's time to
pay the bill I said I call the waiter
you know then I told my friend you know
hit you pay here's my credit card
you pay for the meal I really have to
pee pee you know then I took
hundred-dollar bill I said give him this
for Tim I said I I said give phone tip
it's okay
giving it's my money okay okay then I
went to the toilet then I didn't pee pee
i'ma open the door a little bit
and I'm watching him you know then he
gave the credit card I can't hear
anything I can just see you know then
he'd give $100 then the waiters like
Danny says ten ways like thing then he
asked for change I think you need change
you know then the weight is like then my
friend is like
you know then I did this like three
times now he he will pay for dinner then
he will give like $20 well yeah he
changed okay so why am I talking about
her one mother called me to meet her son
for it in northwest America called
Oregon and the son is artistic you know
he cannot speak well and his mind is
confused you know and she she told me
how how to plant seed for him then I
said you cannot plant a seed for another
person then she said how is he going to
change you know
and take him to the Children's Hospital
okay unlike christmas now it's christmas
right and buy some toys and toy in his
hand and give to the other child okay
and then the other time we'll take then
you and he will plant a seed okay
there's not much intention but there is
giving and slowly his mind will change
and so she said okay I will try and she
did it for like a year and not every day
but you know every week or two weeks
then I went back to their house she said
I want to show you something and she
said okay give get enough song he went
to the piano and he's like he played
perfect song
you know then she said his mansion
okay so it's the rich guy in the
restaurant theory it's the same
principle tricked them to plant seed
okay and and then they start it it's not
fast but it's it's steady okay so find
ways to get the children to help each
other and their seeds will change but it
takes a lot of patience and you are very
cool to even help those children I think
we should give you a head
lasting the disruptive children who are
cannot sit down
special suggestion where's the quality
in your teacher come from come from you
understand okay I don't have to explain
if you do if you do more meditation and
try to be more calm the children in your
class will start to change their
behaviors coming from you so you can use
both strategy
okay cool
break first or performance first Tim do
you know performance first we're gonna
have our performance and then we'll take
a break oh my allied title bout sadaebu
Santo pupuce on top Championship Tiger
the students ofin Omaha it's a chance to
take the Union returns and she died at a
detention
well it was an ally say can see that
item but she talked almost the entity
nation which you can purchase oil in a
Township
Tessa was and you need that en Tasha
hurry owed India while sounds you can
imagine a change to the hormones a
cuidar Suleiman
Erica how's LC o Athenians our helmets
and the Susan that is she would hear
firsthand aha Tabasco Jesus's hands also
that tillu take a chance on that Susilo
ashes Scythian how many single entity
who poverty Sawalha science in another
city or my children go to my home but
your case its interminable up where you
see allows just ok so counter and are
you thousands or by our sea remains in
see one soon as the haunted house since
I went into Hudson Bay our Castle ah ok
like that ok
when the teacher gave this teaching now
never lost sutala tickets also the show
and he was one of the teachers of my
teacher Peshawar the losses that she's
on you a loss when my teacher was a
young man that were Larson a second en
tiendas Soho he was about 18 years old
and he was not a good student
he was a bad boy in his monastery many
times the monks will not wear shoes
so my lama he didn't study
he will get thumbtacks small nail and
put them near the gate then the monk
will come in you know
then he's you know so then during the
during this teaching and other similar
teaching by this lama Pabon car
approaching
my teacher was chosen as to help with
the cooking then he's not supposed to
have time to go to the teaching because
his teacher said you are such a bad
student
it won't help you you can cook then one
day the pop uncle will imitate this
teacher
oh this dinner is very delicious can you
introduce me to the coop then they
brought my teacher to see him then he
said ah looks like a good boy then he
put his hand like this then my teacher
like then after that he became the best
guy in the city they had our competition
15,000 months and my teacher called Anki
Dumbo means the number one okay like
that okay
okay good so each day when the teachers
start a new day they will quote some
famous book to help the student to get
the correct motivation and on the
fifteenth day he quote from aryadeva
this is the number one student of
Nagarjuna then he said Donegal today
lotta number country Yamanashi Danny
Ching wanna get patina came in here
Daniel got a deal a ton number con do
you mean our life is like an ocean of
suffering many many problems this body
itself has bomb inside it will die it's
just time it's going then then the bomb
will go we were we are built this way
from my mom
she killed Danny he caused a cheeky
cheeky means in English if you are mad
at somebody who's acting like crazy like
those kids in the class we call Chiba
in English I'll teach you some bad
English okay everybody learns the bad
words first in each language okay then
someone is not acting nice you can say
you acting like a two-year-old because
when kids get to be two years old they
are always acting bad so here are you'd
ever
he said she could meet your two year old
you are to your own in Buddhism when you
say you act like a trio it means you are
not thinking about coaching
okay you don't understand coaching okay
so you can be 90 years old and you can
be a two-year-old okay because you are
not not using seeds you spend a lot of
money you take a lot of time you go to
Thailand every morning you meditate that
the teachers good quality coming from
you and you go to the past liar and you
find the seed and then on the way home
in the Bangkok Airport you have fight
with your husband what you will have
then you forget husband come from you
maybe you can hold a pen in your hand
when you go to the airport then husband
say something
you're fat don't love me okay
- you need to Milan so if you don't do
that
Ching hua means you will be handcuffed
okay no freedom jig patina came in gear
and then you should be a friend
handcuffed to this body you cannot get a
better body okay mundo can launch a pod
or dude on man jitters always subchannel
damn Barzini so then it's traditional
the teacher will try to get your
motivation better and then review a
little bit about what we did before so
what we did yesterday or the day before
we are studying the two causes of this
body okay one is seeds karma second is
the the thoughts which cause us to do
those common jealousy anger desire
hatred okay so this part of the Lamia
we are going to start psychology class
we're going to study all the parts of
the mind good parts and bad parts
Buddhist psychology is very old about
2,000 years old and it's very beautiful
there are 51 different functions in the
month if you want to learn it some day
talk to the abbey dharma translator in
our group okay this one okay okay that's
his job
correlate and okey-dokey up allocations
accounted ordered a temple on Georgia
song done then he talked about it would
be nice to change this body it's nice to
make money money's nice and it's nice to
have good relationship but at the same
time get a new body okay before you get
too old don't wait till the last minute
okay pack your suitcase this afternoon
don't wait for tomorrow it will be
nervous too late
you will leave something in the bathroom
okay same with this body okay don't wait
until you are 80 years old pack today
tomorrow you can be nice you can have a
nice last day in China change the body
this year the rest of life you can relax
same thing okay
she will Namas my gumption to color it
dunya some we're gonna do that tomorrow
morning it's a tradition at the end of
the meditation to bring the teacher to
the top of the hill small then they come
down into your heart
and then keep them there in the morning
then you talk to your teacher you know
would you stay in my heart
the rest of the day and they will say
yes I will stay in your heart if you
think about me then we have to be honest
I will try but I'm very busy you know I
have many things to think about
then the lama was saying okay just think
about me when you have a big problem
think think about me in your heart if
your husband yell are you your kids
going crazy then check in with the Lama
I'm having a hard day not going so well
then he's like hyung
okay then okay so that's tradition we'll
do it tomorrow
ten times economy team back on dota
minutiae sorta then during the day carry
your manual with you I carry my backpack
everywhere I go I carry is traffic has
conching or not yeah I don't like
traffic I hate traffic during the
traffic is so nice five hours to Bangkok
you can study hold on me you are so
lucky
okay this is the kong king of traffic
understand okay okay tell us something
engine keep it's a me then how to get
that strong mind i want to change this
bunny
Korowai Dickie Tom George so counting
and did a Louie to change then when you
see like I don't know nice car Tesla
Model X we went to dinner at the mall in
Shinji note engine yeah and there was a
model x test line actually I don't know
what it is
that's why go is Stanley and Allison
they are young and they keep my
education case not look Model X you know
like what's modeling I thought there's a
fashion model then this book says when
you see that car
remember conscious okay remember
conscience okay
why if you don't remember conscious
that car will hurt you okay understand
anytime you see beautiful thing a flower
beautiful person beautiful CSP students
singing about Olin butter okay you have
choice you can remember the cookie or
you can just enjoy like blind man okay
you always have choice okay so when the
CSP students sing that beautiful song
you can just enjoy don't think about
coaching then you are burning karma but
you are not making Newcomb
okay your debit card is charging okay so
always try to remember cooking can i buy
tesla guitar sure it's okay in my bad
person in my bad buddhist if i have a
nice car
tell me how you think about the car do
you remember the Kangxi of the car okay
how do I think about the coffee in the
car
because I really want one I want to have
a Tesla and I want to be a good Buddhist
at the same time so teach me how then
just come just remember the conquering
of the car we went to the mall we were
lost you remember yeah we were looking
for a restaurant we got lost in the mall
we actually got to the restaurant after
they closed because we are lost you know
that Stan is very smart he he found the
manager he said I know you are closed
but my friend from America he heard
about your famous restaurant and he
really want to have dinner here tomorrow
he's going to Shinji so I think you
better allow him to have dinner right so
we got dinner but this when we got lost
accidentally we meet the Tesla car
that's why we're late to dinner
cuz boys have to look at the car so when
you look at the car you have to think
where did this car come from why did I
get lost and meet the car by act by
accident
it's a Tesla state in my mind who made
Tesla cars I did okay
I made this cool car okay so then you're
thinking about the conquering of the car
how to get a Tesla car I have to make
more money no you have to help other
people get to where they want to go if
you if the person need a ride to the
Bangkok Airport tomorrow you must take
care of them you must take
responsibility even if it's not your job
why because you understand the
conscience of the Teflon the person who
understands Kong seeing that sign of
understanding coming they are the person
who will help the other person to go to
the Bangkok Airport
okay I'll show you person who doesn't
understand coaching Oh Steve Steve want
to get to the airport tomorrow
he missed the bus Gessler can you help
me no I'm sorry
I'm studying conscience I'm too busy
Galya helping me to get to the airport
is studying kanji understand okay cool
alright so when you see the car you have
to understand if you don't think about
how it's coming from why it's like the
pen then you have to get the car the old
way you know make more money work harder
don't share with other people collect
collect collect then buy a car I got in
my life I never had a new car and then
recently my friends bought me a new car
it was a surprise I didn't pay anything
okay so that's how you get a car okay
understand okay help other people to get
to the Bangkok Airport
that's a special seat for a new car
that's the Kong King of Tesla okay good
then he's complaining about some
Buddhist people they they have a wrong
attitude about the car
if you're good Buddhists you should use
the old broken car you know like that
okay
he's complaining about it this is not a
correct idea about sansara samsara
doesn't mean everything is suffering it
doesn't mean that samsara means if you
don't understand where things come from
the scene then you will use the car and
you will lose the car because you don't
know how to keep the seat going yeah
that's my new car okay they don't make
this color you cannot buy this color
then I just mentioned I like this color
you know then my friends too sent a new
car to Las Vegas they took it up every
piece of park
and they paint each one special paint
sent it back it took like six weeks okay
so I didn't pay anything I think the
paint is cost more than the car okay but
my car is very lonely person my car is
very lonely person I think I drove it
two times because I'm too busy okay so
that's a wrong idea well I shouldn't
have nice car I shouldn't go to a nice
restaurant I shouldn't buy nice clothes
you know don't think like that if you
wear nice clothes so who's my fashion
adviser
Stanley I always take him to the store I
say standing what should I wear what's
cool then I will choose a shirt you know
he's like llama I love you I respect you
that's a super ugly shirt then I'm like
what's a good shirt you know he will
help me to buy this okay
it's not bad to to just nice this
morning the people who get performance
CSP students the ladies look hot the men
look handsome that's good
why it makes other people happy
okay this is a goal of Buddhist if you
look like a flower you make everybody
happy
that's why it takes ten into the store
okay so it's not a bad thing but you
must share with other people
okay those help the refugees okay help
the people in China in the earthquake
you see send them clothes okay both okay
send them clothes and wear nice clothes
okay that's a real Buddhist both okay
good clothes without helping the other
people's clothes is a mistake it's also
mistake to never wear nice clothes okay
we are nice clothes and send money to
the earthquake in West China to buy
clothes that action is not Sun sorry you
are out of samsara okay since RS the
other to wear the fancy clothes and
ignore the earthquake victim or send
money to the earthquake victim and don't
wear nice clothes okay
those two are both sons are how to get
out of samsara send money to earthquake
victim for clothes
then go with family to the mall and buy
some nice clothes because it makes other
people happy
okay that's the motivation it's fine
okay it's fine okay
this CI level 10 is new we just did it
first time in Germany right and now
we're doing it in Guangzhou right no
Taiwan sorry yeah yeah that's level 10
then many people ask me just like what's
the 11 what's level let me don't ask me
it's secret big secret okay you are my
friend enlightened shopping just kidding
just kidding
everybody's exciting okay maybe I will
do a little bit okay that's then you are
out of samsara okay then it's not Sun
sorry